(240) 427-7143 Washington, DC 20009 jjadams1195@gmail.com LinkedIn Profile

Jasmine Adams

Through multiple industry positions and a master's degree in public policy, I have significant professional and academic experience conducting methodologically rigorous quantitative and qualitative research. Drawing on management and social science disciplines, I've engaged in every step of the research and program evaluation process, from designing survey questionnaires and data collection procedures to preparing, analyzing, and presenting insightful results. I am conversant with data visualization and transformation techniques in R and Tableau and have extensive experience using SQL, Excel, and Stata/SPSS for data preparation and analysis. With a background in Marketing and Program Evaluation, I understand how to collaborate with diverse teams on economic/policy research and business development projects and can organize and communicate complex insights in a way that resonates with stakeholders. I continue to develop my professional skills through work in Organizational Behavior at YES Research Lab in the McDonough School of Business where I mentor and manage projects for a team of six Junior Research Assistants.

As a curious and meticulous problem-solver, I strive to work in an inclusive and stimulating environment that enables me to enhance my subject matter expertise through pertinent and impactful projects. With my unique combination of academic and industry experience, I am ideally positioned to deliver thoughtful data analyses, compelling publications, and invaluable recommendations that measurably advance your organization's goals.

I'd appreciate the opportunity to speak with you about how I can contribute to your organization's mission. Please feel free to contact me at your earliest convenience.

Jasmine Adams, MPP

Jasmine Adams, MPP

(240) 427-7143 Washington, DC 20009 jjadams1195@gmail.com

Education

Georgetown University

Master of Public Policy MAY 2023

University of Pennsylvania

Bachelor of Arts in Music and Political Science MAY 2017

Organizations

McCourt Student Association (MSA), Director of First Year and Incoming Students

Georgetown Public Policy Review (GPPR) Podcast Team Member

National Society of Collegiate Scholars

Skills

Programming Languages

HTML, CSS, SQL, Markdown, R

Tools

Power BI, Tableau, Qualtrics, Survey CTO, SurveyMokey, GitHub, Excel, SPSS, Stata

Certifications

CITI Program (Group 2)
Google Data Analytics
ProTools Operator Certificate

Summary

Github.com/JasmineAdams/Portfolio

A diligent and versatile researcher with 5+ years of professional experience. Striving to uncover evidence-based solutions to pressing problems in a position that expands my aptitude for high quality research, consulting, and data analysis.

Work Experience

YES Research Lab, McDonough School of Business JAN 2022 - PRESENT

Senior Research Assistant

- Supporting research in organizational behavior by conducting literature reviews, designing and editing survey experiments and questionnaires in Qualtrics, cleaning and analyzing unstructured datasets in Excel, and editing peer-reviewed journal publications
- Mentoring and managing projects for a team of 6 Junior Researchers
- Graded 50+ projects and case study assignments for the Executive MBA course on organizational behavior in the McDonough School of Business

Just Results, LLC

JUN 2022 - JAN 2023

Research Analyst

- Consulted and conducted impact evaluations for economic development organizations (i.e., the UN International Labor Organization, the World Wide Web Foundation, and USDA)
- Provided evidence-based recommendations by synthesizing mixedmethods research findings using Dedoose/NVivo, Stata/SPSS, and Excel
- Produced impact evaluation reports, data visualizations, and client presentations using PowerPoint and R

FS Investments

JUN 2018 - AUG 2021

Marketing Analyst (promotion)

- Collaborated with the Chief U.S. Economist, the Research Team, and the UX Design Team on economic and financial market research publications and client-facing presentations
- Managed deliverables, coordinated with external and internal partners, and collected and reported statistics for 100+ Marketing-led webinars, forums, and events using CRM databases, SQL, Excel, and Tableau
- Assessed the impact of Marketing activities on brand awareness and sales by tracking analytics and soliciting client feedback through SurveyMonkey

FS Investments

MAR 2018 - JUN 2018

Sales Coordinator

- Streamlined administrative workflows by querying Salesforce reports, organizing expenses, and supporting database management through data entry and data quality control
- Boosted lead generation for 5 regional teams through event planning, project management, and strategic client outreach
- Revamped Sales training materials and procedures to support onboarding